Blake Campbell Resume

Blakecampbell.dev@gmail.com (775) 842-2100 (Reno, NV)

Summary

(Mid-Level) Front-End Developer. Working with AngularJS (1.X), JavaScript, HTML, CSS and Ruby daily for better part of three years. Creating single page applications with clean and reusable code. As the primary Front-End Developer. I work best within small/medium sized teams.

You can view of my public projects through my GitHub linked at the bottom. Email me if you'd like to talk or have any questions.

Experience

MortarStone LLC

Front-End Developer

Sept. 2014 - Current

Building/Maintaining/Testing a financial analytics web application built on AngularJS and Rails for both churches and non-profits. Using AngularJS to handle states in a single page application. Building modules, filters and services to create reusable code for data driven reports.

Experian-Data-Dictionary

OpenSource Project

Feb. 2015 - Current

Experian-Data-Dictionary is an OpenSource translation library for Experian output files. 5000+ Downloads, includes testing. Maintained and created by me. Using vanilla Ruby. Check the link below to the repo.

Meetup Presentation

Presentation

Dec. 2015

Presentation I gave to the Reno Developer Group. Creating/testing Dynamic PDFs made with Ruby on Rails (Prawn Gem). Including examples use cases and building from an API.

Education

TMCC

Aug 2012 - Dec 2014

Truckee Meadows Community College: Started as a Math Major then Physics, finally settled on Computer Science. Got a job in the field before completing my degree. I've been working as a full time developer since then. Average GPA: 3.7 throughout my time there.

Skills

- HTML5 - CSS3

- SASS - JavaScript

- AngularJS 1.X - VueJS

- NodeJS - Ruby on Rails

- Git - SQL

- Grid Frameworks (ex: BootStrap) - OSX

Email GitHub LinkedIn Experian

